<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Matsuura Tomoya</title>
    <link>http://matsuuratomoya.com/en/works/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Matsuura Tomoya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://matsuuratomoya.com/en/works/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>送れ | 遅れ / post | past (rev.2)</title>
      <link>http://matsuuratomoya.com/en/works/post-past_sotsuten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://matsuuratomoya.com/en/works/post-past_sotsuten/</guid>
      <description>Nominated for 23rd Campus Genius Award(Art Section).
2017/2/10~2&amp;frasl;12 At Tokyo University of the Arts Senju Campus
Exhibited at Tokyo University of the Arts Graduation Exhibition(Music Creation and the Environments) 2017
 Thanks to Kuroishi Sayako, Masuda Yoshiki, Tsuji Yurika and more   Acoustic Delay line memory is the memory apparatus used with early electronic computer in 1950s.
Acoustic delay line memory is the system that detect pulse from speaker with microphone, and transmit that pulse to speaker again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spectraspectacular(AMC Soundproject 2014)</title>
      <link>http://matsuuratomoya.com/en/works/spectraspectacular/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://matsuuratomoya.com/en/works/spectraspectacular/</guid>
      <description>At AMC SOUND PROJECT 2014
AMC（Tokyo University of the Arts, Art Media Center）Archive Website
 Sound Application work made in a Project &amp;ldquo;AMC SOUND PROJECT 2014&amp;rdquo;
Project Description (Translation by me)
 We started this workshop project with the theme &amp;ldquo;Music adapted to the enviroments&amp;rdquo;, that makes the interactive Music application/works available on iPhone from last half of 2014. Its purpose is explore the possibilities of future music/sound in today&amp;rsquo;s situation, including portablity of music player or the way to treat the sound media in which we can easily play music via streaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio⇔Visual</title>
      <link>http://matsuuratomoya.com/en/works/audiovisualfeedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://matsuuratomoya.com/en/works/audiovisualfeedback/</guid>
      <description>at Tokyo University of the Arts Class in 2014 &amp;ldquo;Interactive Music 2&amp;rdquo; AMC Archive Page General Info The sound takes visual&amp;rsquo;s infomation, the visuals draw sound&amp;rsquo;s wave. Each of information are transformed interactively. Application was developed with Openframeworks (both of sound and visual). GUI was made with Puredata. Screenshot Pd patch System Audio→Visual The visual was constructed with 6</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How-ring</title>
      <link>http://matsuuratomoya.com/en/works/how-ring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://matsuuratomoya.com/en/works/how-ring/</guid>
      <description>Exihibited at Senju Art Path 2014（Tokyo University of the Arts, Senju Campus annual exhibition）
Description The circular cable, hanged on the space, is connected from a microphone to (actually, via PC,) to Speaker.
When people intercept between the microphone to the speaker, howling(audio-feedback,Larsen effect) occurs. The volume was set to be stable, not overdrived.
A timber of the effect varys from the things or state of interception.
Usually a micophone and speaker will not be set to face-to-face.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>